We shouldn't be here
when it gets dark.
Set the trap at the mouth
of the cave, please.
You need a doctor?
I am a doctor.
It's impressive, don't you think?
Vampire bats weigh almost nothing,
but they can down a creature
nearly ten times their size.
Wow.
What are you using as bait?
You volunteering?
Leaving.
Pay me now.
Before the sun goes down.
You throw in that bushcrafter
on your belt and we have a deal.
Come on.
Move!
Should be able to
take better care of you here.
Everyone's here to help you.
Michael, this is Lucian.
Lucian, Michael.
Michael knows more
about this place than I do.
Play nice.
Hello.
Hello, Milo.
My name's Lucian.
The person
who was here before was Milo.
No.
He was also the new Milo.
And before him
was the other new Milo.
I don't even remember the first Milo.
How long have you been here?
Long as I can remember.
- And you're still not cured?
- There is no cure.
There's something missing
from our DNA.
Like a piece of a puzzle.
And until they find it,
the only way to stay alive
is an oil change three times a day.
What would you do
if you could be normal?
Just for an hour?
I don't think about it.
Hey, look at the freaks!
Look at them!
Best not to be outside
when school gets out.
Like the original Spartans,
we are the few against the many.
Milo?
Nurse?
Okay...
Lucian.
Lucian!
With one of these?
It took a team of scientists
to build that machine
and you fixed it
with a ballpoint pen?
There's a school
for gifted children in New York.
I think that I could get them
to agree to cover your tuition
and provide private care
to help manage your condition.
Somewhere you could study,
learn, hone your skills.
You have a gift, Michael.
I don't think I could forgive
myself if I saw it go to waste.
"Dear Milo,
"this isn't goodbye.
"I'm gonna find a cure for us,
"so we can be cranky old men someday.
"Your friend, Michael.
"P.S. You shouldn't
have unfolded this.
"Now you'll never
get it back together.
See you this summer."
No.
"Dear Milo..."
Please, can I have my letter back?
- What?
- Please, can I have my letter?
Okay. Here.
Please. Ah!
Please!
Stop.
Go away!
Let me have a look.
He tried to steal my letter!
Milo, Milo, stop.
Stop. Stop. Stop.
What about Milo?
I'll look after Milo.
He needs me.
Michael Morbius
completed his doctorate by 19
and quickly established himself
as the world's leading authority
on blood-borne diseases.
His development of artificial blood
has saved more lives than penicillin.
Michael Morbius,
please step forward
to acknowledge
the receipt of your prize
from His Majesty, the King of Sweden.
I can't believe you
dissed the king of Sweden.
The king and the queen,
their loyal subjects,
all of Scandinavia and
the entire scientific community.
Yeah, but who does that?
Well, Anna, we both know
I have issues.
But, hey, I kept the program.
There you are.
- Hey, Dr. Bancroft.
- Hey, Anna.
- We going to play?
- Oh, I don't think so.
See, now that Dr. Morbius
is back,
maybe you should
try losing for a while,
- see how that feels.
- Not gonna happen.
- Michael.
- Uh, yes?
- You got a minute?
- Of course.
New one. For your collection.
Dr. Morbius is in trouble.
I'm in trouble.
"I can't accept a prize
for the by-product
of a failed experiment."
- Lab 1.
- Front page,
"American Scientist
Rejects Nobel Prize."
You know that people
actually like writing checks
to Nobel laureates?
Makes them feel better
about their investment.
It would help if you stuck
around long enough to cash them.
You're pushing yourself
too hard.
Does our generous benefactor, Milo,
know what you're actually doing here?
What am I actually doing here?
Remixing human DNA with bat DNA.
- I have no idea what you're...
- Talking about?
Is anything ringing a bell?
No bells ringing. Uh...
Okay. Maybe this
will jog your memory.
I wouldn't go in there if I were you.
That is a...
- It's a fish tank.
- Hmm.
Like, for...
flying mammals.
Oh, I see.
Some friends I brought back
from Costa Rica.
So when were you gonna tell me?
More importantly,
how did you get my pass code?
It's the first six digits
of pi backwards.
It's your password for everything.
You should change that.
You could lose your license for this.
I'm not gonna need it
much longer, doctor.
You, on the other hand, will.
You know, there's something
called "plausible deniability."
You should be thanking me.
These are the only mammals on Earth
that have evolved
to feed exclusively on blood.
So in order to drink it,
these bats produce saliva that
contains unique anticoagulants.
So your theory is, if you can
successfully splice
vampire genes into your DNA,
it would allow your body to produce
those same anticoagulants.
Yes.
It would be a cure.
At what cost?
The fusion of different species
is a legacy
we already carry in our bodies.
Viruses insinuating
their nucleic acid onto our own
over hundreds of thousands of years.
That's evolution.
This is different.
I don't think it is.
We have to push the boundaries,
take the risks.
Without that,
there is no science.
No medicine.
No breakthroughs at all.
Okay.
Test subject
for cell combination 117.
Come on, come on, come on.
Test subject 117 has resulted in...
failure.
I don't wanna see you get hurt.
I should've died years ago, Martine.
Why am I still alive
if not to fix this?
To save my best friend, Milo.
And everyone else like us.
Not like this.
Dr. Morbius, it's Anna.
Her temperature's spiking,
and her kidneys are shutting down.
We have to induce a coma
before she has a stroke.
A hundred milligrams of propofol.
- Sure.
- Now.
Come on.
It's okay.
It's okay. We got you.
There you go.
Thank you, nurse.
We're gonna let you sleep a bit.
Take a nice long nap.
- Michael.
- What?
It worked.
Dr. Michael Morbius.
Some
crippled guy's here to see the Boss.
Michael! Get over here!
As long
as I am a cripple you'll be fine.
♪ Stop dreaming
Of the quiet life... ♪
You're late.
I was trying out
this new thing
called "working."
Oh, yeah. I don't believe
I'm familiar with the word.
I don't believe you are.
So, what's up with the goon squad?
Oh, I won a hand of cards
against some Russian gentlemen.
Apparently they found
his luck improbable.
- There you are.
- More like impossible.
So, doctor,
how is our favorite patient?
Still determined to make
his short life even shorter?
Yes, I am.
Anyway, you're one to talk.
You look terrible.
Look at the state of you.
Says the man wearing...
What is that, a quilt?
Oh, sorry. I didn't get the memo
to dress for a funeral.
Right. I will see you later.
And you...
my door is always open.
We miss you at Horizon.
We could use your mind.
- I'll leave you two to your fun.
- Bye, Nicholas.
I have some good news.
Let's go for a walk.
How's Martine doing these days?
Dr. Bancroft?
She is, uh, overqualified,
outperforming, brilliant as usual.
And a royal pain in my ass.
But she's keeping me honest for
the most part. Why do you ask?
Eh, no reason. Just haven't
seen you in forever.
I wondered if she had
something to do with it.
Aw, I miss you too.
But, yes, she has been working
with me to save our lives.
I could ask her to stop if you
like, put us out of our misery.
Just don't do something stupid
and go and fall in love
because, believe you me,
there is absolutely no cure for that.
Says the guy who knows
absolutely nothing
- about the subject.
- Not true.
I read about it
in books all the time.
- Books, really? Wow.
- Yeah.
Or romantic comedies.
The point is...
The point is, love is not
on the cards for us, my friend.
Listen, if you start quoting
The Notebook to me,
I am going to stop
and hobble very slowly
in the opposite direction.
Throw it!
I'm close, Milo.
I can feel it.
A cure.
It's finally possible.
- Seriously?
- Highly experimental.
Ethically questionable.
Very, very, very expensive.
- I knew that was coming.
- And not exactly legal.
Oh, and it has to be done
in international waters.
You were always expensive.
Is it dangerous?
Should I be worried?
- You want me to lie to you?
- That would be nice, yes.
It's a walk in the park
on a sunny day.
Oh, yeah, that bad, eh?
Listen.
We don't have much time left.
This could be our last chance.
So, what do you say?
We go out with a fight?
Yeah.
You with me?
Till the day you die, brother.
Till the day you die.
You'll have everything you need.
We're the original Spartans, mate.
- The few against the many.
- Yeah.
You know, I'm sure you're cheating.
No. No, you're not.
What you got?
Putting another one in the oven.
Wish me luck.
The moment of truth.
Success, Martine. We did it.
It's holding together.
Test 243.
Human trials.
I'm glad it's you.
Had a lot of other suitors,
didn't you?
Yeah.
You know, the whole near-death thing
is very, very chic.
I read it in Cosmo.
Do they still make Cosmo?
I don't know.
I know it's just
what you always wanted.
Could be a collector's item
one day, you never know.
This better not be my last one.
I know this is painful,
but you got it.
- That's it. Bingo.
- Right there.
Almost there, almost there.
It's all right.
Come on. Come on.
There you go.
You can buckle me up.
- Yeah.
You all right? Great.
I call.
- Bringing out the big guns.
- Let's go again.
I'll be back.
I'm gonna check on the doctor.
All right.
- You shouldn't be down here.
- I can be wherever I want, nurse.
It's "doctor," actually.
I'm afraid
you're gonna have to leave.
Doctor. Sure, I can see it.
But, uh, you're still the help,
just like me.
Wow.
You can tell all that
by just looking at me, huh?
Here I thought you were just
another jacked-up dumb shit.
Get out.
Michael?
- Michael?
- Where is he?
Don't move.
What the hell?
Everybody down to the lab now.
Roger that.
Don't shoot!
Michael!
Stop!
Michael.
It's just me.
Michael, please.
Michael, stop!
Stop! Please!
You're hurting yourself! Stop!
Hey! Step back! Move!
- Stop. Put that gun down...
- Move!
Shit. Close it! Close it!
What the hell is that thing?
- Fall back! Fall back!
- Shit.
- Let's move.
- Go, go, go!
Johnny!
Get out of here!
Sweeping Level 3.
Jason, come in.
Jason. Jason?
Oh, shit.
Son of a bitch!
Shit! Oh!
Oh, shit!
Martine.
Oh, my God.
Mayday, mayday, mayday.
This is the LCV Murnau.
Call letters 3-X5Y.
We are 13 nautical miles
off the coast of Long Island.
Request immediate airlift.
Repeat, this is the LCV Murnau.
Mayday, mayday, mayday.
It's up here to the right.
FBI Agent Stroud.
Can we have the room, please?
You heard the man.
Can we please have the room?
If you could start exiting,
that'd be fantastic.
Well, we haven't had
anything this good
since that thing in San Francisco.
Uh, eight bodies,
running IDs right now,
but apparently they all shop at
the same mercenary supply store.
Uh, one survivor,
a Dr. Martine Bancroft.
- Can we talk to her?
- If she wakes up.
Uh, she fell down
and hit her head, apparently.
- Anything else?
- Someone made a mayday call.
- Not Dr. Bancroft.
- Nope.
It was a male,
didn't identify himself,
then wiped
all the surveillance footage.
He grew a conscience
and jumped overboard?
It happens. Oh, and get this.
All the bodies that you're looking at
are nearly drained of their blood.
So, what hunts at night
and drinks human blood?
You're gonna love this.
Early this morning
an unmanned cargo ship was discovered
near the eastern tip of Long Island
with multiple bodies on board.
Authorities are not making
any comment at this time.
But there are reports
of one survivor,
and we have learned
from a high-ranking Coast
Guard official
that the vessel was flying
a Panamanian flag
when it drifted in
from international...
What's happened?
Some kind of accident.
How's your pain today?
On a one to ten?
Eleven.
I'm sorry.
You're going to be okay.
Lab 1.
Privacy screens.
Come on. Come on.
As a result of my procedure,
I have an overpowering urge
to consume...
blood.
Human blood.
In certain respects, I have succeeded
far beyond anything
I could have imagined.
For the first time
in my entire life, I feel...
good.
Yesterday, I could barely walk.
Today, I don't know
what I'm capable of.
For a period of time after ingestion,
my numbers are off the charts.
I have the constitution
of an Olympic athlete.
Increased strength and speed
that can only be described as...
superhuman.
And all of this...
on artificial blood.
I've become something different.
I feel a kinship
with these creatures.
They would tear anyone else
apart, but they welcome me.
Like a brother.
I've even developed
a form of echolocation.
Bat radar, for the uninitiated.
The question is:
How do I control it?
Isolate it?
Breathe.
And let it go.
But, unfortunately,
this condition is temporary.
I've been timing myself.
Artificial blood keeps me
stable for six hours.
But that window...
is growing shorter.
Artificial blood won't work forever.
One question remains:
What if...?
What if artificial blood
becomes ineffective?
What happens if I go without?
No blue...
No red...
Nothing.
Eventually, my vitals
drop precipitously
and my illness returns
with a vengeance.
Soon, I'll face a choice.
Drink the red...
or die.
But what happened on that ship...
can't ever happen again.
Michael.
It's me.
You in here?
Where are you?
Michael?
Michael? What are you doing?
Michael, it's Milo.
What are you doing?
Do you need help?
What?
"Blood."
You want the blood
in the freezer? Wait.
I'm coming, I'm coming.
I'm coming.
Michael, hang on.
Here. Here.
Michael...
You're... You're strong.
Michael.
You did it.
You found a cure to live.
Michael.
What? What is it?
I've made a terrible mistake, Milo.
We all make mistakes.
Don't worry about it.
You've never made
one like this before.
Michael, enough.
Just give it to me. I need it.
I can't live like this
any longer. Please.
- I can't.
- What do you mean, you can't?
- I need this. I...
I've done things, Milo.
I killed people.
W-we... We can make that go away.
The ones on the boat,
they're thugs, guns for hire.
- I can make that go away.
- You don't understand.
I do understand. Please.
Have I ever denied you anything?
Said no?
Have I always given you...?
I can't control it!
What, so... So you get to live
and I get to die? Is that it?
It's a curse.
Believe me, brother. It is.
Now, please, I need you to go.
- It's not safe here.
- No.
No, don't make me go.
Please, Michael, don't...
I said, get out!
Milo.
She's right here.
Dr. Bancroft?
Agents Stroud and Rodriguez.
How you feeling, doctor?
Like I'm in a hospital,
eating really crappy Jell-O.
This shouldn't take long.
You were out on a container ship
that washed up off of Long Island.
Doctor, there were
eight dead bodies inside.
We also noticed that their blood
was... What do you call it?
Exsanguinated.
I looked it up.
So, um, sorry for the graphic nature
of some of these photos.
But, um, you're a doctor,
so you know what people
look like on the inside.
These puncture wounds right there,
those look like fang marks to you?
Well, you were out there
conducting a major experiment.
We're just hoping
you could shed some light.
Yeah, that...
Not exactly sanitary, isn't it?
I'm having a little bit
of a hard time
remembering what happened that night.
Sure. Let's go.
You also work
at the Horizon Lab, right?
With Dr. Michael Morbius.
Yes.
Appreciate your time, doctor.
Hello?
Who's there?
Get away from her.
Just step back.
Has she been there all night?
Looks like all the blood
was drained from her body.
- Any contusions?
- Not that I can see.
Back to our rooms, okay?
Dr. Morbius?
Agent Stroud.
Agent Rodriguez.
Can we have a minute?
Of course. How can I help you?
First, I wanna say thank you.
Your artificial blood
actually saved my arm
in Afghanistan, sir.
I'm glad I could be of service.
I mean, I must admit, doc,
you don't look
anything like you do on the news.
Yeah, you look downright robust.
I have good days and bad.
Pilates helps.
How are you on boats?
As you can see...
don't have very good sea legs.
Why do you ask?
'Cause you've been looking for a cure
for your condition
your whole life, right?
You've pretty much tried everything.
Crazy experiments, maybe on a boat?
"Crazy" isn't a term
that I would use...
detective.
Unorthodox, maybe.
But I'd do just about anything
to save a life.
I'm sure you can understand that.
Anything else I can
help you two with?
All
units, the 120 block, Horizon Labs,
female body drained of blood,
initiate lockdown.
Copy that. Doc, got
a couple more questions for you.
Yeah, you're coming with us.
Hey, freeze!
Stop him!
Hey!
Hold fire!
Get backup and meet me up top.
Enough.
It's worse than I first thought.
At this rate, artificial blood
will stop working
in a matter of days.
8:13 p.m.
Down from six hours
to four hours, 22 minutes.
I got a problem.
Holy water?
- Really?
- What?
I'm not taking any chances.
It's triple blessed.
We found this little guy
on the container ship...
with those bodies.
That's a little hobby
of yours, right?
You know, eight dead mercs on a boat
really doesn't ruffle our feathers.
I'm pretty sure
they were guilty of something
and happy to have them off the water.
But Nurse Sutton, single mother
with twin girls, that's...
- something else.
- Yes, I know.
Her name was Kristen.
We worked together
every single day for seven years.
She was a good person.
So why'd you do it?
I can't answer that.
What did you do to yourself, doctor?
- Make us understand.
- I wish I knew.
Okay.
Great stuff.
Um, Really informative.
- Thank you. Uh...
- I dropped a bag.
There's something inside that I need.
- Bag of artificial blood.
- Yeah.
Yeah. It's in evidence,
I'm sorry.
I'm starting to get hungry.
And you don't wanna see me
when I'm hungry.
We're done here. Let's go.
Guard!
Your lawyer's here.
You look terrible.
Lawyer, huh?
I don't remember
you ever finishing law school.
'Cause I didn't.
Sit down. Sit down.
I mean, if one of us
was going to end up
in bright orange trainers,
I would never have guessed
it would be you.
They're charging me with murder.
I don't know. I don't know.
I...
Maybe I blacked out? Uh...
Hey.
Now listen to me.
I don't believe it.
You're not capable of that.
I know that all you've ever
tried to do is help people.
You don't belong here.
This place is for terrorists
and drugs lords and God knows who.
Michael, we need
to get you out of here.
In whatever way possible.
Maybe this is where I belong.
If I'm in here,
then nobody else dies.
Listen to me.
You are not capable
of killing that woman.
Hey, Your Highness, time's up.
Michael, here's something
to keep you going.
Guard.
Never too early.
Milo.
Milo!
Let's move!
Come on, this way!
Let's go. Let's go.
Open the door.
Now! Go!
He's getting away!
Daily Bugle, please, sir.
- There you go, buddy.
- Here you are, my friend.
Always figured that guy for a freak.
How's that?
You've never met him.
I mean, look at him.
What else you need to know?
You know, you shouldn't
judge someone by how they look.
Didn't your mother
teach you any manners?
Take me, for example.
I may look harmless enough.
Do you think I'm joking?
Milo!
Got me.
You see? I knew you could do it.
You took the serum
even after I warned you.
What am I gonna do, lay down and die?
- Thank you for the death wish.
- I tried to protect you!
Protect me?
Protect me from what?
Becoming a monster like me.
I don't think you're a monster.
Okay?
I killed the nurse.
I know. But you know
what it's like your first time.
You have no idea what you're
doing. You have no control.
No.
Milo, you have to stop.
You have to stop. You have
to stop denying who you are.
It's boring. We can go anywhere,
we can do anything. Let's go.
Let's have some fun.
This isn't you.
I know you. Where's the brother
that I used to have?
How can you say that to me?
Look what you've become.
Everything I am, I am because of you.
I looked up to you my whole life.
I will never leave you,
and I will not go back.
You cannot make me go back.
I won't let you make me go back!
Move, bitch, move!
- Goodness.
- Whoo!
We've evolved!
You're a scientist, Michael.
Surely, surely you understand that.
That's not what this is.
This is a mistake.
But I can fix it. I'll figure
out how to reverse it.
Artificial blood will keep us
stable until I do.
Yeah, I'm fine just the way
I am, thank you very much.
Hey! Hands up!
- Up against the wall. Now.
- Officer.
- Come on.
- Anything you say.
- You. Don't move.
- Okey-dokey.
We have the suspects.
Like we used to say...
live a little.
Hey!
Freeze!
All our lives, we've lived
with death hanging over us.
Why?
Why shouldn't they know
what it feels like
for a change, Michael?
Michael!
Michael.
I'm not gonna fight you, Milo.
Now he's laying out
officers in my city, huh?
It's unforgiveable.
Just keep your eyes
on Dr. Bancroft.
Yeah.
Woman in the jeans, where'd she go?
Yeah, right.
Great.
Hey, stranger.
Michael?
You shouldn't be here.
I didn't kill Nurse Sutton
or the police.
Or any of those people.
I know.
Milo, he...
He took the serum.
He's out there.
And I have to stop him.
But I need your help.
Coffee?
- No, thanks. I quit caffeine.
- It's decaf.
Not that kind of vampire.
Just checking.
I shouldn't have dragged you
out there. I'm sorry.
You didn't.
I wanted to be there.
Well, then apology rescinded.
I guess we're both a little crazy.
How do you feel?
Incredible.
I mean, I went from dying
my entire life
to feeling more alive than ever.
Thankfully, artificial blood
keeps me stable.
I just have to drink it more often.
- How often?
- Uh...
Every four hours, 22 minutes.
Down from six.
It's losing its effectiveness.
The issue is,
when it stops working...
I'll become like Milo.
You won't.
Hi. Over there.
Sorry, this one's no good.
Check it again.
And keep one for yourself.
No, I don't wanna do it.
There's plenty more
where those came from.
Come on, man,
we gotta get back to the lab.
Michael?
Okay, I know that look.
You're up to something.
What is it?
I'll need a couple of things
from the lab.
- Can you do that for me?
- Yes, I can.
But you didn't answer
my question. What is it?
You're right.
I'm up to something.
- You got the blood?
- Got it.
The ink on this
new batch is pretty legit.
It's a good thing
we switched the chemicals.
Yo, finish up.
It's a nice place that you got here.
Oh, I love this movie.
Is this the part
where the mysterious guy
with the hoodie comes in
and kicks everybody's asses?
I love that part.
- Who the hell are you?
- It doesn't matter,
but I am gonna need your laboratory.
You can keep the money,
all your little toys.
Just leave the science-y stuff
and that bag of spicy Cheetos.
- He wants my lab?
- Yeah.
You trying to be funny?
No, no, no. Absolutely not.
That's their job.
I mean, look
at their matching necklaces.
Time to go.
Did you know that there are
27 bones in the human hand?
Allow me
to introduce the phalanges.
The metacarpals.
Shit.
Let's get the fuck out of here!
And the pretty, little stinky pinkie.
- Who the hell are you, man?
- Me?
I am Venom.
You can go now.
Six to eight weeks,
a little ibuprofen.
Should heal up just fine.
Yo. Can I get a tequila, please?
Don Julio 1942.
Do I know you?
Me?
- Yeah.
- No, I don't think so.
We've met.
- I'm sure of it.
- No, I'd remember.
You're too pretty.
You know what they say, "Tequila
to remember, whiskey to forget."
That's good.
Sir, two tequilas, please.
Hey, yo.
Her drinks are spoken for, bro.
Salute.
You know, uh, ahem,
I'm gonna do you a favor
and let you walk out of here,
all right?
That's very kind of you.
Here was I thinking
you were a complete asshole.
- Sir, can I get my friend here...
- Relax.
...and his friends
a round of whiskeys?
Hey!
I'll get you another drink.
Hey.
Another time.
Jerk.
You see the size of that guy?
I'm not paying for those drinks.
Martine.
Milo.
Sorry. I let myself in.
I hope I didn't startle you.
It's okay.
If I'd known
our biggest funder was coming,
I would have planned
a nice dinner for us.
Actually, I've already eaten.
Whatever it is, it's doing
wonders for your health.
I feel great.
- What can I do for you?
- Well, it's Michael.
I'm worried about him.
He's alone out there.
And I think he needs me.
If I can get to him before
the police do, I can help him.
You wouldn't happen to know
where he is, would you?
You two have always been so close.
I'm sorry.
I don't.
Hmm.
Just to be sure,
I'm going to ask you one more time.
You don't happen to know
where he is, do you, Martine?
I wouldn't lie to you, Milo.
I don't.
Now, if you don't mind,
I have work to do.
Okay.
Well, if you see him,
if you hear from him, tell him:
"We are the few
against the many."
We'll have to do that dinner
another time, Martine.
Police!
Clear!
Here, kitty, kitty, kitty, kitty.
Cat's gone. And she's
probably gone along with it.
It's time to eat, you little monster.
Oh!
Shit.
Michael?
Hey.
Michael.
I'm sorry.
You may wanna close that up.
Yep.
How does it feel...
when you're on red?
Something wakes up
inside of me, something...
primal.
And it just, uh...
And it wants to hunt.
And wants to kill.
I'm sorry.
Hi.
Good as new.
Nice work, doctor.
Thank you, doctor.
You know, for the record, I...
I wasn't gonna go
full Dracula on you downstairs.
For the record...
I find him to be quite the romantic.
Come here.
Just close your eyes.
Okay.
Move closer.
Did you know the average male
body has 12 pints of blood?
I mean, how much do you think
the doctor can drink?
I don't know.
When's the last time
you had 36 beers?
you had any beers?
CCTV.
I'll go grab the footage.
I don't want you
to have to move or anything.
All right, check this out.
Wait, wait, wait.
Zoom in. And hold right there.
That's not the doctor.
It's what these
bloodsuckers do. They multiply.
Breaking news on the Lower East Side
where three people have been killed.
Authorities have confirmed the
discovery of three new bodies
outside a bar popular
with Wall Street traders.
And like the victims before them,
they were completely drained
of their blood,
earning the killer
the moniker "Vampire Murderer."
The prime suspect, renowned
scientist Dr. Michael Morbius,
remains at large.
What have you got yourself into?
However, another source
inside the department
has told us that CCTV footage
of the murders
suggests the killer
could be a copycat.
Residents are being urged
to stay home after sundown
until the killer, or killers,
are brought to justice.
Milo?
You've discovered my secret.
I mean, look at me.
I am reborn.
I am the resurrection.
My God, what have you done
to yourself?
What?
Do you disapprove?
What's the matter, Nicholas?
Is Daddy cross?
All right. Settle down.
Let's go and have a drink together.
Come celebrate with me, please.
- No.
- Just one drink.
Milo, you're scaring me.
Please. Just...
Just... Just calm down.
- What's the matter?
- I can't... I can't sleep.
I can help you with that.
I've been more than a friend
to you all this time, Milo.
And I'm going to stay here with you.
But there will be
no more violence, understand?
That doesn't do it for me.
I should have known.
You always take his side.
Tell me your side, then, Milo.
Michael doesn't accept
what he is, Nicholas.
I'm gonna make him accept it.
- By ruining his good name?
- See? There! There you are!
Perfect Michael, selfless
Michael, Michael the favorite!
Don't be childish, Milo!
If anyone has a claim
to being my favorite, it's you.
- I've devoted my life to you.
- Liar.
You pitied me before.
You did. You pitied me before.
You're repulsed by me now.
I am repulsed...
by what you've done,
by what you've become.
Whatever this thing is...
you're not up to it.
There's no shame in what we are.
"We are the few..."
"Against the many."
Tell Michael,
you tell him I'm going to kill
as many as I want.
"He's only destroyed
by a stake through the heart,
made from the wood
of the Holy Cross."
You don't believe this.
No. But after the week
that I've had, anything is possible.
What is that?
This is an antibody.
It inhibits ferritin,
induces a massive iron overload,
instant hemochromatosis.
Deadly to bats, fatal to humans.
Okay.
Who's the second one for?
My window's closing.
We both know that.
By tomorrow I'll be forced
to consume human blood.
I can't do that.
I won't do that.
So this is your solution, huh?
Injecting yourself with poison?
I brought this into the world.
It's up to me to take it out.
I need you to go now.
It's not safe here. Okay?
Nicholas, you okay?
Michael, I need help.
I went to see Milo.
Nicholas?
Nicholas!
Nicholas.
Nicholas?
- Michael.
- Come on,
we have to get you to a hospital.
You have to stop him.
Michael.
Call out for him.
I want him to hear you.
- No.
- Yeah.
I won't ask you again.
Say, "Michael."
Michael.
Good girl.
- Michael.
- Yeah.
Michael.
Milo.
You're hurting me.
It's okay.
Martine?
Let me take a look. Martine.
- Let me look.
- It's bad.
Michael.
Make it mean something.
I can help you.
I'm sorry.
Drank the red.
Good for you.
It's just you and me, Michael!
Nothing, no one, to hold us back.
I'm all you have left.
That's the spirit. Yeah.
Bye.
Come on, Michael!
Come on!
You can do better than this!
It's not a curse.
It's a gift.
You started this, you created this,
you created us!
Michael.
You can't kill me.
I mean, it's me.
You gave me my name.
Remember?
I remember everything.
I'm sorry.
Lucian.
- Stay back, people.
- Get back! Back!
Hope the food's better in this joint.
The bizarre story developing
at the Manhattan Detention Center
when a man identifying himself
as Adrian Toomes
simply appeared
in an otherwise empty cell.
A hearing has been set
that could likely lead
to his immediate release.
Thanks for meeting me, doc.
I've been reading about you.
- I'm listening.
- I'm not sure how I got here.
Has to do with Spider-Man, I think.
I'm still figuring this place out,
but I think a bunch of guys
like us should team up.
Could do some good.
Intriguing.